[{"category": "Actors & Actresses", "questions": [{"answer": "Chuck Norris", "question": "Which actor traveled with the circus at the age of 15 and was a tamer?"}]}, {"category": "Art / Culture", "questions": [{"answer": "Verona", "question": "In which city did Romeo and Julia live?"}]}, {"category": "Australia", "questions": [{"answer": "Opera", "question": "What is the most famous building in Sydney?"}]}, {"category": "Biology", "questions": [{"answer": "Yes, a snail has 135 rows of teeth", "question": "Do snails have teeth?"}]}, {"category": "Dinosaurs", "questions": [{"answer": "Torosaurus", "question": "To which dinosaur does the largest skull belong?"}]}, {"category": "Economy", "questions": [{"answer": "Drachme", "question": "What was the currency of Greece before the introduction of the EURO?"}]}, {"category": "Film / TV", "questions": [{"answer": "Antonio Banderas", "question": "Who played Che Guevara in the movie \"Evita\"?"}]}, {"category": "Food and drink", "questions": [{"answer": "Vitamin C", "question": "Which vitamin is the only one that you will not find in an egg?"}]}, {"category": "Fruits & Vegetables", "questions": [{"answer": "52 meters", "question": "How long was the longest apple peel, recorded in the Guinness Book of Records?"}]}, {"category": "General", "questions": [{"answer": "Dardanelles", "question": "For which narrow sea strait is Hellespont the ancient name?"}]}, {"category": "Geography", "questions": [{"answer": "The Mediterranean Sea and the Red Seas", "question": "Which two seas are joined by the Suez Canal?"}]}, {"category": "History", "questions": [{"answer": "Russia", "question": "Which country sent its navy around the world to fight the Japanese in 1904?"}]}, {"category": "Informatics", "questions": [{"answer": "File Transfer Protocol", "question": "What does \"FTP\" stand for in the computer and internet world?"}]}, {"category": "Language", "questions": [{"answer": "Montreal (Canada)", "question": "Which is the world s second largest French-speaking city?"}]}, {"category": "Literature", "questions": [{"answer": "Rudyard Kipling", "question": "Who wrote Jungle Book?"}]}, {"category": "Music", "questions": [{"answer": "Megan Thee Stallion", "question": "Who is Tina Snow?"}]}, {"category": "Nature", "questions": [{"answer": "Elephant", "question": "Which mammal cannot jump?"}]}, {"category": "Politics", "questions": [{"answer": "The White House", "question": "In which house does the American president live?"}]}, {"category": "Science", "questions": [{"answer": "Blue or purple", "question": "What is the color of giraffe tongue?"}]}, {"category": "Sports", "questions": [{"answer": "Seven times", "question": "How many times has Michael Schumacher been a Formula 1 champion?"}]}]